{
    "subject": "resource/Tagalog_Republic",
    "predicate": "property/commonName",
    "object": "Tagalog Republic",
    "human_readable": "The common name of the Tagalog Republic is Tagalog Republic.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9817706942558289,
            "question": "What is the common name of the Tagalog Republic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9242445230484009,
            "question": "Is 'Tagalog Republic' the official name of the country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7268588542938232,
            "question": "What are some notable characteristics of the Tagalog Republic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7245615124702454,
            "question": "Who are some prominent figures from the Tagalog Republic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6356436014175415,
            "question": "Where is the Tagalog Republic located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5895732641220093,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about the Tagalog Republic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5604943037033081,
            "question": "What language group does the name 'Tagalog' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5442743897438049,
            "question": "How would you describe the culture of the Tagalog Republic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.49574488401412964,
            "question": "What are the main political institutions within the Tagalog Republic?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48627999424934387,
            "question": "What is the history behind the establishment of the Tagalog Republic?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The common name of the Tagalog Republic is Tagalog Republic.",
            "html": "dbpedia_452_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the main political institutions within the Tagalog Republic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_452_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How would you describe the culture of the Tagalog Republic?",
            "html": "dbpedia_452_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What language group does the name 'Tagalog' refer to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_452_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_452_87.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents do support that the common name of the Tagalog Republic is \"Tagalog Republic\" as it is directly mentioned in the first document provided."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}